Nijat Dursunlu

Front-End Developer



- Baku, Azerbaijan
- +994 51 361 30 25 nicatdursunlu

 - in nijat-dursunlu (H) nicat_dursunlu

Skills

Design (Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD)

Front-End (React JS, React Router, Redux, Redux Toolkit, TypeScript, Vue JS, Vue Router, Vuex, Vuetify, Material UI, JavaScript(ES5/ES6), HTML, CSS(Sass), Bootstrap, Responsive design)

Mobile (React Native, Expo, Redux, Redux Toolkit, Firebase)

Back-End (Java core, Java SE, OOP, Spring(Spring Boot, Spring Data), JPA, Lombok)

Version Control Systems (GIT(GitHub, GitLab))

General (Data Structures, Algorithms, Jira, Swagger UI, Postman, Slack)

Soft skills (Teamwork, Problem solving, Communication, Adaptability, Attention to details, Responsibility, Time Management)

Languages

Azerbaijan	• • • •
Russian	• • • •
English	• • • •
Turkish	• • • •

Profile

I have more than a year of experience on Software Development. During this period I did my best with understanding my responsibility and learning required new technologies asap to be part of new projects. It is a priority to me to catch up with deadlines and do my utmost as team member or individually.

Professional Experience

Junior Software Developer, ATL Tech ☑

10/2021 - present | Baku, Azerbaijan

- Attending sprints and completing daily tasks
- Projects: Performance Management System, Dövlət Vergi Xidməti, N3(FHN)
- Used tools and technologies: React JS, Redux, React Router, Material UI, Vue JS, Vue Router, Vuetify, Vuex, SASS, GitLab, Jira, Swagger UI, Slack

Software Developer Intern, *ATL Tech* □

04/2021 - 07/2021 | Baku, Azerbaijan

- Attending sprints and completing daily tasks
- Project: Talhunt Admin Panel
- Used technologies: Vue JS, Vue Router, Vuetify, Vuex, SASS, GitLab, Jira, Swagger UI

Education

Bachelor / Computer Engineering(ENG),

Baku Engineering University ☑ 09/2017 - 07/2022 | Baku, Azerbaijan

• GPA: 95.63

Courses

Mobile Development,

ABB Tech Academy(DAN IT education) □ 02/2020 - 07/2020 | Baku, Azerbaijan Certificate with Honors 17

Certificates

 You can see all the certificates I received from the link below \(\mathbb{Z}\)